A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Politics - New York City Office, Series J.1 FA345
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Politics, General, 1935-1970; 1; 9 Document Box(es)
  - New York Republican State Committee, 1950-1967 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    Correspondence & memos; program for 1957 Presentation of Irving Ives Award to Vice President Nixon.
  - New York Young Republican Club, 1956-1962 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    General correspondence.
  - Poor, Henry V., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    Candidate for U.S. Congress against Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jr., seeks NAR advice.
  - Republican National Committee/Republican National Finance Committee, 1947-1966 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    Miscellaneous correspondence of committee; Republican Women's fund raising for the 1956 campaign; polls 1954-1955; 1950 Len Hall [US Congressman from New York, head of Republican Congressional Committee statement, chairman of Republican Congressional Committee.
  - Republican Open Forums, 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    General correspondence, lists of contributions; letters of thanks; memos re usefulness of forums.
  - Republican Open Forums, 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 0068A)
  - Republican Party, 1952-1963 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    Address by Helen Edmonds of North Carolina College on the challenge faced by the Republican Party in 1960 & the implications for Republican Women; memorandum from Jacob Javits to Eisenhower, 1954; planks of Republican & Democratic platforms, 1944 & 1948.
  - Republicans - NYS, 1954-1962 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    General correspondence with NYS Republican office holders with NAR on party issues.
  - Republicans - States other than NY, 1954-1963 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    Requests for NAR contributions to candidates; requests for contributions to committees, most declined; correspondence with candidates.
  - Republicans - States other than NY - Alabama & Southern States, 1954-1963 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Republicans - States other than NY - Illinois, 1954-1963 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Republicans - States other than NY - Maine, 1954-1963 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Republicans - States other than NY - New Jersey, 1954-1963 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Republicans - States other than NY - Rhode Island, 1954-1963 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Santiago, Mrs. Laura, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    Correspondence with owner of small radio station regarding campaign activities.
  - Scranton, William, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    Background material on the Pennsylvania Governor's bid for the Republican Presidential Nomination.
  - Speech Material & Notes - General, 1951-1955 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    NAR notes & outlines for speeches; general background material dealing mainly with achievements of Eisenhower administration; letters of thanks for material; Stacy May material re inflation, draft speech; economic affairs background material.
  - Speech Material & Notes - NAR Notes, 1951-1955 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Speech Material & Notes - Penn State University Commencement Speech, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Speech Material & Notes - Penn State University Commencement Speech, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Speech Material & Notes - Political Background, 1951-1955 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Stassen, Harold, 1945-1952 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    Correspondence with the Governor of Minnesota and presidential candidate; campaign contributions.
  - United Republican Finance Committee (NYS), 1947-1962 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    Miscellaneous correspondence; meetings 1959 and 1962.
  - Westchester County (NY) - General, 1958-1967 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    Miscellaneous correspondence, telegrams & memos; comparison of Westchester voting statistics, 1953-1957; 1958 GOP News; background on Mount Pleasant [NAR home voting district].
  - Westchester County (NY) - Westchester pre-election report, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Westchester County (NY) - Westchester Republican County Committee, 1947-1966 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    Correspondence & telegrams with Ed Michaelian (chairman). Herb Gerlach as well.
  - Westchester County (NY) - Westchester Republican County Committee, 1947-1966 (Box 9, Folder 0088A)
    Correspondence and telegrams with Ed Michaelian (chairman).
  - Westchester County (NY) - Yonkers Republican Organizations, 1954-1958 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    1956 yearbook; report of survey to improve political campaign techniques; YRCC news releases.
- National Political Campaigns, 1956-1968; 2; 19 Document Box(es)
  Subseries 2 is arranged chronologically by campaign, and thereunder alphabetically by subject.
  This subseries contains correspondence and memoranda on the activities undertaken by Rockefeller in President Eisenhower's 1956 campaign and Rockefeller's three successive presidential campaigns. In 1956, Rockefeller served as an alternate delegate to the Republican National Convention for President Eisenhower. Within a year of being elected Governor of New York in 1958, Rockefeller considered running for the Republican party nomination for president. However, in December 1959, he terminated his campaign and asked that all efforts to draft him as a candidate be suspended. Rockefeller also unsuccessfully pursued the Republican party nomination in 1964 and 1968. This particular subseries, and the subseries that follows, offers a limited perspective on the dynamics of these campaigns.
  - 1956 Presidential Campaign - Republican National Convention (Box 10, Folder 90)
    Correspondence; NAR served as NY delegate at large, schedules, memos; excerpts from transcript of Eisenhower news conference; directory of NY delegates & alternates; summary of news & comments on convention.
  - 1956 Presidential Campaign - Republican National Convention (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - 1956 Presidential Campaign - "Ike Day" Committee (Box 10, Folder 92)
    CBS coverage of "Ike Day," October 13, 1956; coverage by other stations; Ike Day Committee Kit.
  - EMPTY FOLDER, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Clippings, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    Clippings & articles re 1960 Presidential election and the prospects for the 1964 Presidential nominations.
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Correspondence, Memos & Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    Correspondence, memos; Nixon's economic policy; NAR's future in government, evaluation of NAR organization; Market Planning Corporation; Republican Finance Committee; reapportionment; viewer evaluation of TV formats; post-election statements; NAR candidacy; proposed political course of action; election analysis; public policy & public relations.
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Correspondence, Memos & Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Correspondence, Memos & Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Correspondence, Memos & Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Fact Books - California Issues, November 1959 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    Compiled primarily by Roswell B. Perkins and George L. Hinman.
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Fact Books - Domestic Issues, Position Papers, June 1960 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Fact Books - Domestic Issues, Position Papers, June 1960 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Fact Books - General Convention Information (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Fact Books - General Convention Information (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Fact Books - Republican Officeholders, State & Federal (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Losee, Tom, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    Portfolios & mailing packets; status report "Public Relations Opportunities"; NAR speech at Economics Club of NY dinner 1959; "The Rockefeller Record"; "NAR: Man with a Mission"; reprint of "San Francisco Chronicle," November 1959 [Losee managed public relations for campaigns].
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - McCann-Erickson, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    Correspondence with the NYC advertising firm; special reports on 1960 legislative session; thoughts on candidacy of NAR for President of U.S., 1959; memos to NAR.
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - McCann-Erickson, Inc., Advertising (Box 13, Folder 107)
    NY Republican State Committee 1960 Campaign: History; Media Estimates; Call Reports & Pertinent Memoranda.
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - McCann-Erickson, Inc., Advertising (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - NAR for President Letters of Support, (A-Z), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    NAR states he will devote himself to governorship and will not seek Republican Presidential nomination in 1960. Statement to "Dallas News."
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - NAR for President Letters of Support, (A-Z), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - NAR for President Letters of Support (A-Z), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    NAR states he will devote himself to governorship and will not seek Republican Presidential nomination in 1960. Statement to "Daily News."
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Republican National Convention - Chicago (Box 14, Folder 112)
    Persons attending; gifts; reservations, etc.; letters of appreciation; campaign budget; state & national committee members.
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Polls & Radio Reports, Inc., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    Republican image poll; Survey of Latin American Public Opinion, 1958; WRCA-TV "Searchlight" interview with Chairman of NY Republican County Committee, December 1959; WNTA-TV "Open End" discussion of public relations & Rockefeller, December 1959.
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Speech Material from Arthur E. Summerfield, Postmaster General (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign - Statements (Box 14, Folder 115)
    NAR statements issued or made on national issues.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - "Citizens for 'X'", 1963 (Box 15, Folder 116)
    Republican Citizens Committee publication on how to organize volunteer committees.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - National Convention, San Francisco - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 117)
    Correspondence & memos; events at convention; leaflets & general information.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - National Convention, San Francisco - Delegations (Box 15, Folder 118)
    Summary information on the individual state delegations.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - National Rockefeller Campaign Committee (Box 15, Folder 119)
    Finance Division summary report, 1964; book with comments, examples of campaign mail before 1964 convention (two copies).
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - National Rockefeller Campaign Committee (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Nixon, Richard (Box 15, Folder 121)
    May 1964 memo and report by Roswell Perkins on Richard M. Nixon's campaign activities.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Operations Committee Meetings, April 1964-July 1964 (Box 16, Folder 122)
    Rockefeller National Campaign Committee confidential records of planning for 1964 campaign. Reports on primaries; reactions to defeat in California.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Press Kit Papers (Box 16, Folder 123)
    NAR summary positions on issues.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - 1960 Platform Analysis Notebook and Melvin Laird Statement (Box 16, Folder 124)
    Two copies.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - 1960 Platform Analysis Notebook and Melvin Laird Statement (Box 16, Folder 125)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Background material on convention delegates (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Convention Delegates, Estimates (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Convention Delegates, Lawyers (Box 17, Folder 128)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Convention Delegates, Preferences (Box 17, Folder 129)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Delegate Book (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Delegate Book (Box 17, Folder 131)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Delegate Book (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Delegate Book (Box 18, Folder 133)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Delegate Book (Box 18, Folder 134)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Delegates on Convention Resolutions Committee (Box 18, Folder 135)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Delegate Reaction to Liberal Platform (Box 18, Folder 136)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Goldwater Positions, January 1963 (Box 18, Folder 137)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Major Speech Outlines (Box 18, Folder 138)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - NAR on Select Issues (Box 18, Folder 139)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - NYS NAR Public Appearances, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 140)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - NYS NAR Public Appearances, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 141)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Out of NYS NAR Public Appearances, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 142)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Out of NYS NAR Public Appearances, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 143)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Rockefeller Campaign Speakers Kit (Box 19, Folder 144)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - "Rockefeller on the Issues" (Box 20, Folder 145)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - "Rockefeller on the Issues" (Box 20, Folder 146)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - Summary Positions (Box 20, Folder 147)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Reports - The Youth Division (Box 20, Folder 148)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Campaign Materials - 1960 Republican State Committee Fact Book (Box 20, Folder 149)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Campaign Materials - Books (Box 20, Folder 150)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Campaign Materials - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 151)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Campaign Materials - "The Rockefeller Campaign Express" (Box 21, Folder 152)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Campaign Materials - Rockefeller on the Issues (Box 21, Folder 153)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Campaign Materials - Rockefeller Papers (Box 21, Folder 154)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Campaign Materials - Rockefeller vs. Goldwater (Box 21, Folder 155)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Campaign Materials - "Win with Rockefeller" (Box 21, Folder 156)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Final Report (Box 21, Folder 157)
    Financial report on the organization's efforts.
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Press Releases (Box 21, Folder 158)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Press Releases (Box 21, Folder 159)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Press Releases (Box 21, Folder 160)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Youth Kit (Box 22, Folder 161)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Youth Kit (Box 22, Folder 162)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President, Youth Kit (Box 22, Folder 163)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Aldrich, Richard S. (Box 22, Folder 164)
    Correspondence and memoranda from Aldrich, chairman of Rockefeller for President.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Clurman, Shirley - General File (Box 22, Folder 165)
    Rockefeller vs. Nixon (speech writing research); requests for campaign materials; schedule objectives; list of campaign staff.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Clurman, Shirley - Happy Rockefeller clippings (Box 22, Folder 167)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Correspondence Urging NAR Candidacy (Box 23, Folder 169)
    Collection of original letters pulled from file by Public Relations Dept. urging NAR to run for presidency in 1968.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Correspondence Urging NAR Candidacy (Box 23, Folder 170)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Correspondence Urging NAR Candidacy (Box 23, Folder 171)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Correspondence Urging NAR Candidacy (Box 23, Folder 172)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - National Convention, Miami, Florida (Box 23, Folder 173)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 23, Folder 174)
    Ann Whitman written letters to citizens on behalf of NAR, affirming public of NAR's support for Nixon.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - General Correspondence & Memos (Box 23, Folder 175)
    NAR letters of thanks; requests for information on the family; Rockefeller for President general campaign staff.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - General Correspondence & Memos (Box 23, Folder 176)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy (A-B) (Box 23, Folder 177)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy (C-E) (Box 24, Folder 178)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy (F-I) (Box 24, Folder 179)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy (J-L) (Box 24, Folder 180)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy (M-O) (Box 24, Folder 181)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy (P-R) (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy (S-T) (Box 24, Folder 183)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy (U-Z) (Box 24, Folder 184)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy - Non-alphabetized letters (Box 25, Folder 185)
    (random order)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy - Non-alphabetized letters (Box 25, Folder 186)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy - Non-alphabetized letters (Box 25, Folder 187)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Republican Presidential Campaign - Letters of Thanks for Support of Candidacy - William Watts - Letters (Box 25, Folder 188)
    Correspondence on NAR's behalf.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Applications (Box 26, Folder 189)
    Requests for positions in campaign program.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Clippings (Box 26, Folder 190)
    Miscellaneous campaign clippings.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Clippings, foreign (Box 26, Folder 191)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Final Reports (Box 26, Folder 192)
    Miscellaneous final reports on the Rockefeller for President organization.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Financial Information (Box 26, Folder 193)
    Memoranda concerning payments made by the Rockefeller for President organization.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Financial Information (Box 26, Folder 0193A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Offers of Assistance (Box 26, Folder 194)
    Correspondence from individuals offering help with the campaign, some NAR replies.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Post-Convention letters of thanks (Box 26, Folder 195)
    NAR letters to individuals with thanks for support during the convention.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Post-Convention letters of thanks (Box 26, Folder 196)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Post-Convention letters of thanks, Rockefeller Family (Box 26, Folder 197)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Post-Convention letters of thanks, Rockefeller Family (Box 26, Folder 0197A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 198)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Special Projects, Fees (Box 26, Folder 199)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Black, Ann (Box 26, Folder 200)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Braun, Barbara (Box 26, Folder 201)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Breckenridge, Carolyn (Box 26, Folder 202)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Chin, Beverly (Box 26, Folder 203)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Clemens, Rosemary (Box 26, Folder 204)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Conway, Karen (Box 26, Folder 205)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Dahler, Sally (Box 26, Folder 206)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Deviney, Maria Alexis (Box 26, Folder 207)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Doss, Martha (Box 26, Folder 208)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Eggers, Anne (Box 26, Folder 209)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Elliott, Martha Ann (Box 26, Folder 210)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Finney, Pamela (Box 26, Folder 211)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Fischbein, Martin M. (Box 26, Folder 212)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Fowler, Dennis (Box 26, Folder 213)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Foster, M. Alice (Box 26, Folder 214)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Frederick, Sharon (Box 26, Folder 215)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Geilich, Geoffrey (Box 26, Folder 216)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Gladding, Rita (Box 26, Folder 217)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Gould, Lynda (Box 26, Folder 218)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Greene, Bobbie (Box 26, Folder 219)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Grzybowski, Marcia (Box 26, Folder 220)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Kenan, Clay (Box 27, Folder 0211A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Kelly, Wesley (Box 27, Folder 0212A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Kieffer, Townsend (Box 27, Folder 0213A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Kissinger, Henry (Box 27, Folder 0214A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Krupenie, Harriet (Box 27, Folder 0215A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Lasky, Minna (Box 27, Folder 0216A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Love, Eleanor (Box 27, Folder 0217A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Martin, Evelyn (Box 27, Folder 0218A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Martinez, Raymond Peter (Box 27, Folder 0219A)